(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T00:26:29.733954",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
While slashing through asphalt tires,
暗闇走りぬける
running through the darkness.
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I surrender to a cheap thrill,
明日におびえていたよ
I was terrified of tomorrow.
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰のために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone's sake,
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何もこわくはない
I'm not afraid of anything at all.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは解けない愛のパズルを抱いて
Embracing the love puzzle we can't solve alone,
Get wild and tough
この街でやさしさに甘えていたくはない
I don't want to rely on kindness in this town.
Get chance and luck
君だけが守れるものがどこかにあるさ
There's something somewhere that only you can protect.
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも傷ついた夢をとりもどすよ
I'll reclaim my bruised dreams, even all alone.
ありきたりの僕の日々を壊してくれ
Destroy my boring days
異常なほどの刺激を待ち望んでいたのかな
I wonder if I was waiting for an abnormal stimulation
ちょっとしたそんな冒険心は改札に吸い込まれて
That little adventurous heart was sucked into the ticket gate
吐き出され辿り着いた雨降るこの街
Spit out, I arrived in this rainy town
何も感じないまま死んでいくのは御免だ
I refuse to die without feeling anything
終わりのその先を目指して
Aiming for the other side of the end
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Run out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなままで
we are still uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
the future is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
we are in the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ so there's no looking back
I want to chase it, so there's no looking back
また首を突っ込んで見事に散らかしてんだ
I stick my neck in again and mess it all up splendidly
曖昧で退屈な気持ちとさらばさ
Goodbye to the vague and boring feelings
関係ないって顔したってどこかで繋がってて
Even if I pretend it doesn't matter, it's connected somewhere
何度だって引き戻すと手招きこの街
This city beckons me to return time and time again
ビリビリ痺れるような今を生きていたいんだ
I want to live in the 'now' that makes me tingle
極限のギリギリで行こうぜ
Let's go to the limit
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Run out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなままで
we are still uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
the future is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
we are in the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ so there's no looking back
I want to chase it, so there's no looking back
inside outside, i just wanna feel good everyday
いっさいがっさい i just want to feel alive
everything, I just want to feel alive
駆け出せ steppin' out tonight
Run out, steppin' out tonight
僕らは不確かなままで
we are still uncertain
輝く steppin' out tonight
Shining, steppin' out tonight
待ってるんだぜ 明日が
the future is waiting for us
抗え steppin' out tonight
Resist, steppin' out tonight
僕らは風の中
we are in the wind
それでも steppin' out tonight
Even so, steppin' out tonight
追いかけてんだ so there's no looking back
I want to chase it, so there's no looking back
don't take your love away
you ain't heard nothin' yet - yet
まだ成り出した表示は
The display that started ringing again
あなた「今忙しいの」
You say, "I'm busy right now"
未読の talk to love call もういっぱいでお世話しない
Unread talk to love call, overflowing and restless
「邪魔をしないでちょうだい」
"Don't get in my way"
Don't take your love away
You ain't heard nothin' yet - yet
You ain't heard nothin' yet, yet
Don't take your love away
Wake up, make up, bang bang
また鳴り出した表示はあなた「今忙しいの」
未読のトークとラブコールもいっぱいで忙しい、「邪魔をしないで頂戴」
突き返す素っ気無い可愛いげないセリフ
こんなので拗ねるなんてまだガキね
本音は言わない方が悩ましい
甘い言葉かけるよりもずっと愛しい
たまらなくなるほど求めて離さないで
キスじゃ足りなくていっそ殺して
predilection
あなたを手にかけて
infatuation
呼吸さえし止めて
dedication
このまま
addictionしてまだたった一口で「終わり」
predilection さあさ口をつけて
Predilectionさあさ口をつけて
infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuationそのまま飲み込んで
dedication すぐさま
Dedicationすぐさま
addictionしてほらたった一口「死ぬほど」愛したいから
Addictionしてほらたった一口、「死ぬほど」愛したいから
Don't take your love away
You ain't heard nothin' yet - yet
You ain't heard nothin' yet, yet
Don't take your love away
Wake up, make up, bang bang
Have it all 愛情過多でいいあなたにはわたししかない
Have it all愛情過多でいいあなたにはわたししかない
Take it off 愛情が足りないわたしにはあなたしかないって
Take it off愛情が足りないわたしにはあなたしかないって
胸を刺したこの手 掴んだ まだ未練があるのね ああまただわ
ワガママ愛と名付けてまた支配する
あなたに溺れてく 息苦しいくらいに
心酔させていっそそうして
predilection わたしを手にかけて
Predilectionわたしを手にかけて
infatuation キスで口塞いで
Infatuationキスで口塞いで
dedication まだまだ
Dedicationまだまだ
addictionしてまだ雑多、非合理な愛
predilection 喉奥流し込んで
Predilection喉奥流し込んで
infatuation 躊躇いなど捨ててさ
Infatuation躊躇いなど捨ててさ
dedication すぐさま
Dedicationすぐさま
addictionしてほらたった一口 これで終わらせないで
Our love's, love's continue to further evolve more
My love, love is besotted with you
You love? Love? Continue to further evolve mo-mo-more!
I'm a little confused
これはあなたとの聖戦 あなたはいつでも正しいわ
アフロディーテはただ愛されたかっただけだったのよ
「わたし以外いらない」 そういう言葉は期待するだけ無駄だって知ってしまった
愛し方が解らないの ねぇ
たまらなくなるほど求めて離さないで
キスじゃ足りなくていっそ殺して
predilection あなたを手にかけて
Predilectionあなたを手にかけて
infatuation 呼吸さえし止めて
Infatuation呼吸さえし止めて
dedication このまま
Dedicationこのまま
addictionしてまだたった一口で「終わり」
predilection さあさ口をつけて
Predilectionさあさ口をつけて
infatuation そのまま飲み込んで
Infatuationそのまま飲み込んで
dedication すぐさま
Dedicationすぐさま
addictionさようなら 真っ赤、吐き出して 息が止まるのよ 今
Addictionさようなら真っ赤、吐き出して 息が止まるのよ 今
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and
I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights
It's time
As our power grows
Tryin' to stop us shows
You might as well go try'n
Stop time
So you know that we're out there
Swatting lies in the making
Can't move fast without breaking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
Ain't it a shame
I'm not a figment of your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as
I'm just as dangerous
As you, so know you'll find
A taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fire inside your head, your heart
And as your crippled brain
Tries to fight in vain
Your empire will fall apart
And you'll know we were out there
Swatted lies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices rang out, here
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI challenging you
I'm not a phantom, I'm in your face and I'm here to see it through
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
Ain't it a shame
I'm not a figment of your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as, I'm just as dangerous
As you, so know you'll find
Taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fight inside your head, your heart
And as your crippled brain tries to fight in vain
Your empire will fall apart
And you'll know we were out there
Swatting lies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
飛べない...ここからじゃ
I cannot fly... from here
横顔眺めてるだけじゃ
I just watch from the side
無力さを嘆いていても
And lament my weakness
この背を誰も押さない
There is no one to push me back
Going out!
飛び方を忘れていた
I forgot how to fly
闇烏たちの嘆きのvoice...
The voices of the ravens lamenting in the dark...
凍てつく無機質な
Of a freezing and inorganic
世界に何を望むの？
World, what do you wish for?
そうだけどね確実な
Yes, but you know, an unyielding
希望がもう僕の中に
Hope is already inside me
Going up!
「何が出来るか」なんてもう
Again, with what can I do?
やってみなきゃワカラナイ
If you don't try, you won't know
走り出した序章へ
Ran to the start
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
Certainly it was decided before my birth
羽根を揺らし強く地を蹴って
Flapping my wings, I lift off strongly from the ground
キミの元へ
And I will go to your side
羽撃たく “ravens!”
Ravens flapping their wings
Fight! keep holding on!
何千のループの中出逢う
Among thousands of ties we meet
この場所で
In this place
もう止められない宿命の真下で
It can no longer be stopped, under this fate
僕に出来る事がどんなに僅かでも
I will do what I can do, as little as it may be
その体に背負うもの
That body was burdened
その痛み分け合える日まで
By the pain until the day it could share it
キミの傍にいるよ
I am on your side
飛び立つ今そこrave on!
Fly now, cheer up!
無理より飛び立つ今
muri yori tobidatsu ima
the rainbow
無性に振り返る自分の居場所探して
mushou ni furikaeru jibun no ibasho sagashite
後悔になぞらえた脆い線を描く夜にた
koukai ni nazoraeta moroi senn o shimbu yoru ni ta
不器用に風に揺れて
fukiyou ni kaze ni yurete
僕はまだ弱いままで迷って壊れてはそうやって続く世界へ
boku wa mada yowai mama de mayotte kowarete wa sou yatte tsuzuku sekai e
片方一つ見つけたら瞬く星を描き進め
katata hitotsu mitsuketara matataku hoshi o egaki susume
闇から覗いた光手を伸ばしてさ行こう
yami kara nozoida hikari te o nobashite sa yukou
走り出したこの想い
hashiridashita kono omoi
ほら心の星が導いて染み付いてる言えない傷をこの翼で運び出す rainbow
hora kokoro no hoshi ga michibite shimitsuiteru ienai kizu o kono tsubasa de hakobidasu rainbow
不器用に風に揺れて
fukiyou ni kaze ni yurete
僕はまだ弱いままで迷って壊れてはそうやって続く世界へ
boku wa mada yowai mama de mayotte kowarete wa sou yatte tsuzuku sekai e
気が付くと僕たちは長いくにして知るんだ
ki ga tsuku to bokutachi wa nagaikunite shiru nda
向かい風に逆らい小さな羽広げ目指そう僕らハデル日まで
mukainikaze ni sakarainichisana hane hiroge mezasou bokura haderu hi made
共にかけてゆくぜいこう
tomoni kakete yuku zeikou
誰のせいでもない涙誇りにしてさ行こう
dare no sei demo nai namida hokori ni shite sa yukou
走り出す始まりへ
hashiridasu hajimari e
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた羽を揺らし強くちぎって君のもとへ羽ばたく rainbow
kitto umareru mae kara kimatte ita hane o yurashi tsuyoku chigotte kimi no moto e habataku rainbow
なんとの後悔の後に生まれるんだこの一瞬が永遠へ変わる手を繋ぎそして世界を見に行こう
nanto no koukai no ato ni umareru nda kono isshun ga eien e kawaru te o tsunagi soshite sekai o mi ni yukou
気が付くにも僕たちはながよりくくりぬけてしるんどその意味を真実へとかけてゆこう
kigatsuku ni mo bokutachi wa naga yoriku rinukete shiru ndo sono imi o shinjitsu e to kakete yukou
遠くの景色にも愛を持てた時に世界はまた生まれ変わる
tooku no keshiki ni mo ai o moteta toki ni sekai wa mata umarekawaru
the rainbow
So far!
Are you guys having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments using the hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
Don't forget to share your comments using
the hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
Hashtag Promise2U!
This way! This way!
All right, we're currently at the Promise hideout!
All right, we're currently
at the Promise hideout!
Over there!
Oh my god, that is huge!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
We're going the wrong way!
No, you're going to die! Don't die!
Oh, it's so big!
Is there a helicopter flying out there taking videos of us?
Is there a helicopter flying out there
taking videos of us?
Now that we have it, and now that we also have such a fancy stage on the rooftop as well and everything, let's turn things up with some fun...
Now that we have it, and now that we also
have such a fancy stage on the rooftop...
Variety games!
Yes, it's a variety pack! I bet you guys are feeling a bit tired after that intense first half of this live, right?
Yes, it's a variety pack! I bet you guys
are feeling a bit tired after that first half!
I'm good! I'm alive, I'm standing!
You guys seem a little tired.
To help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness, I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys.
To help you recover from that fatigue,
I've prepared the perfect segment!
Yes, it's called Pleasure or Pain? Promise Fist Massage Karaoke Battle!
Yes, it's called Pleasure or Pain?
Promise Fist Massage Karaoke Battle!
What does that mean? Feet?
Each of us will sing one chorus from two songs they're good at! Battle it out by total score using the scoring system.
Each of us will sing one chorus from two songs!
Battle it out by total score!
Foot pressure point massage while singing... Can they hold out and finish the song?
Foot pressure point massage while singing...
Can they hold out and finish?
And how that will affect our performance or score? Well, we'll see and find out together.
And how that will affect our score?
Well, we'll see and find out together.
And there'll be a punishment for the losers as well, of course.
And there'll be a punishment
for the losers as well, of course.
Place 2nd or lower and drink the super sour geki-suppa juice as punishment!
Place 2nd or lower and drink the super
sour geki-suppa juice as punishment!
Now let me show you the key item that can make or break this battle. Here's what we use for the first round.
Now let me show you the key item
that can make or break this battle.
It's a foot reflexology mat! I've never stepped on one of these before.
It's a foot reflexology mat!
I've never stepped on one of these before.
Wait, so you want us to sing while we walk on this? You're going to walk on this?
Wait, so you want us to sing
while we walk on this?
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Senpai! Senpai!
I feel like... you look so beautiful today.
You know, I feel like as a senpai, you should show us how it's done, right? I'll go first.
You know, I feel like as a senpai,
you should show us how it's done, right?
You know, it's got to come out from complimenting me like... oh you look so amazing!
You know, it's got to come out from
complimenting me like... oh you look so amazing!
I'll show you how it's done! Yes, let's go!
I'll show you how it's done!
Yes, let's go!
All right, so IRyS, which song are you going to sing? I am going to sing Zankyou Sanka.
All right, so IRyS, which song
are you going to sing? Zankyou Sanka.
If you're ready, get on the mat! Yes!
Let's get on the mat! Get on the mat!
Come on, don't be dramatic.
Oh, she's fine! She's fine! She's like the music girl. That's not so bad.
Oh, she's fine! She's like the music girl.
That's not so bad.
誰が袖に咲く幻花
Who is the phantom flower
that blooms on the sleeve?
ただそこに藍を落とした
I just dropped blue there.
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when colors dissolve gaudily,
銀朱の月を添えて
with a silver-vermilion moon added.
転がるように風を切って
Cutting through the wind like rolling,
脈打つごとに強くなった
growing stronger with every pulse.
光も痛みも怒りも全部 抱きしめて
Embracing all of the light,
the pain, and the anger.
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If you aren't chosen, just choose.
声よ轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Let your voice roar
beyond the night.
涙で滲んでた あんなに遠くの景色まで
Up to scenery blurred by tears,
so far away.
響き渡れ
Let it echo across!
何を奏でて？ 誰に届けたくて？
What are you playing?
Who do you want to reach?
不確かなままでいい
It's fine to remain uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も どんなに長い葛藤も
No matter how dark the emotions,
no matter how long the struggle,
歌と散れ 残響
scatter with the song, reverberation.
I can barely balance on this.
You need good, right? Good. Oh, there you go. Oh, my god.
How's your blood flow? Do you feel... How do you... Do you feel refreshed?
You look great.
All right, looks like the score is in. Shall we see the score?
Oh, this is what you got! Ta-da!
I've never I've never gotten a score that low with...
I've never—I've never gotten a score that low with...
70.161. That's so good! That's good!
That's good? What are you talking about? You know, 70, that's a... that's a...
that's a C. No, B. That's a B.
That's a B minus! B minus! Yeah, that's good!
Is it a B minus? That's a C! That's a C minus! No! It's a B minus!
All righty then, who wants to go next?
Senpai! Senpai! Senpai janai!
Senpai! Senpai! Not senpai!
We're from... We're from the same...
She's senpai by two hours. Was it two hours? Yeah, I think it was around two hours.
Oh, okay, I guess.
Oh god! Oh god! I'm going to have so much fun!
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you going to sing for us?
Um, I'm going to be singing Mousou Zei!
Wow, Mushroom Mousou Zei! Yay, cuz I only know old songs! Yay!
Wow, Mushroom Mousou Zei! Yay, 'cause I only know old songs! Yay!
I know that song!
Okay then. All right, please start the music. Music, start up!
She's so confused!
あの子もいいな あの子もいいな 頭の中でイイコトしてる
Don't you think she's alright, doing good things in her head?
あなたはそれで満足ですか？ 叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Are you satisfied with that? Don't you want to make it come true?
あの子でいいや あの子でいいや 妥協大好き 飲む針千本
Anyone is fine, compromise is great, swallowing a thousand needles.
あなたはそれで満足ですか？ 叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Are you satisfied with that? Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう 妄想税 皆様の暮らしを豊かにするために
Let's pay the delusion tax to enrich everyone's lives.
叶えたいを現実に 今、未来を買い戻せ
Turn what you want into reality, buy back the future now!
アレしたい病も 欲しがりも さあ、痛いのその向こうへ
The sickness of wanting things, desires too—now, beyond the pain!
そう、汚い妄想は 汚いお金で解決させましょう
Yes, dirty delusions should be solved with dirty money.
あなたはそれで満足ですか？ 叶えたいとは思いませんか？
Are you satisfied with that? Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう 妄想税 皆様の暮らしを豊かにするために
Let's pay the delusion tax to enrich everyone's lives.
叶えたいを現実に 今、未来を買い戻せ
Turn what you want into reality, buy back the future now!
アレしたい病も 欲しがりも さあ、痛いのその向こうへ
The sickness of wanting things, desires too—now, beyond the pain!
そう、汚い妄想は 汚いお金で解決させましょう yeah!?
Yes, dirty delusions should be solved with dirty money, yeah!?
Oh! You did... You did amazing!
I feel like that brought out like a like a roughness.
I feel like that brought out like a—like a roughness.
Wow! Did I actually sing on that?
Oh, wow. Blood circulation. That's a lot of blood circulation.
All right, the score is in. Let's see what Kronii got.
73.864 pts.
Wait, wait, it's still first half. I can still make it. I can still make it.
All right! Oh god, my turn! Yeah! Let's go!
I'm excited. I've been wanting to sing this song for so long.
Okay, what song is it? What are you singing?
Fairy Tail! Yakusoku no Hi!
Finally! I finally found an instrumental track. I'm so excited. Your childhood, I'm assuming.
Trout? Not really. Not really. Okay. Nice fairy tale.
Now, okay, now that you're ready, please hop onto the foot reflexology mat.
Come on. Yes. Don't fail me.
フェアリーテイル この手で掴んだ光は
Fairy Tail, this light I grabbed with these hands
夢に描いた理想郷 夢のまま終わらせない
is an ideal world painted in dreams, won't let it end as a dream.
An ideal world painted in dreams, won't let it end as a dream.
いつか会える 未来の僕に伝えたい
Someday we'll meet, I want to tell my future self
時に未来は残酷で 鏡のように割れるけど
sometimes the future is cruel, breaking like a mirror,
欠片を失えないよう 見付け出せばいい
but so as not to lose the fragments, just find them.
凍える闇が 僕たちの行く手塞いでも きっと忘れない 希望
The freezing darkness may block our path, but we'll never forget hope.
フェアリーテイル この手で掴んだ光は 絆の力溢れているから
Fairy Tail, this light I grabbed with these hands is overflowing with the power of bonds.
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know those sad tears,
だから譲れない 揺るがない
so we won't yield, we won't waver.
夢見た あの日に そう 辿り着くまで
Until we reach that day we dreamed of.
You guys can sing on this thing.
It brought something in, from deep within.
Okay, then. Since you have something deep within, it's time to see what we've got for you.
Hi.
Whoa, she got an 81.434!
Currently in first place is HeyCo's Bails with 81.434 points. Any comments heading into the second half?
I'm excited. I'll continue to do my best so that I don't have to do the juice content!
All righty then, let me introduce the next key item, or should I say person for the second half?
In this foot massage battle, yeah?
ではお入りください、どうぞ！
Please come on in, go ahead!
こんにちは。
Hello.
Okay, let me introduce you guys to Takita-san, who will be giving us foot massages, foot massage pro.
よろしくお願いします。
Pleased to meet you.
こわい。
Scary.
こわいね。
It's scary, right?
痛いです か？
Does it hurt?
痛いです。
It hurts.
Okay, so let's get. Who wants to kick things off?
Since I went last last time, I'll go first this time. What are you going to sing? That is right, that is true.
Um, I'm going to be singing Baka Mitai! Let's go!
Okay, then please get ready. Takita-san, please take care of us.
優しくしてくだざい。
Please be gentle with us.
大丈夫、健康にいいんだから。
It's fine, it's good for your health!
Let's go!
Okay, then please, let the music start!
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I've been a fool, you're such a child,
夢を追って傷ついて
you got hurt chasing dreams.
嘘が下手なくせに 笑えない笑顔見せた
You're so bad at lying, but still showed me that unconvincing smile.
I love youも ろくに言わない
You don't even say "I love you" right,
口下手でほんまに不器用
so awkward and truly clumsy.
なのに なのにどうして サヨナラは言えたの
So why, why on earth were you able to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ あんたが 好きで好きすぎて
It's no good, no, it's no good at all, I love you, I love you way too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも 歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
No matter how strong the drink, unyielding memories... are just foolish.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Oh, that was a beautiful ending to that song.
That's scary, oh my god.
All righty, how was that? How was the song while getting a foot massage?
I can't feel my big toe!
Now the score is in, let's see what you got.
You got a 68.057! Hey, over 50, so close to a good number, yeah.
痛かった。ありがとうございました。
It hurt. Thank you very much.
健康になった、you became a bit healthy. A lot healthy, huh?
You became a bit healthier. A lot healthier, huh?
Is it really that bad? Oh my god.
You're not exaggerating, are you?
やってよ!
Do it!
I want to try.
Okay, go!
I'm gonna sing Usseewa!
All righty, please get ready. Tachita-san mata yoroshiku onegaishimasu.
All righty, please get ready. Tachita-san, we're in your care again.
よろしくお願いします
Please take care of us.
ガチ痛い！ガチ痛い！
That really hurts! It really hurts!
Anone, I'm little...
Um, I'm a little...
You're done. You're done. You don't have to worry.
Yeah! Okay then, let's go!
正しさとは 愚かさとは それが何か見せつけてやる
What is right? What is foolish? I'll show you what they are!
ちっちゃな頃から優等生 気づいたら大人になっていた
I've been an honor student since I was little, and before I knew it, I was an adult.
ナイフの様な思考回路 持ち合わせる訳もなく
With a thought process like a knife, as if I could ever have that.
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない 困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
But I haven't played enough, something's missing, it's troubling, whose fault is this?
あてもなくただ混乱するエイデイ
Aimlessly just getting confused, ey-day.
それもそっか 最新の流行は当然の把握
Or maybe so? The latest trends are naturally understood.
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Checking economic trends during my commute.
純情な精神で入社しワーク 社会人じゃ当然のルールです
Joining with a pure spirit, working hard, it's only natural for a member of society.
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ あなたが思うより健康です
Shut up, shut up, shut up, I'm healthier than you think.
一切合切凡庸な あなたじゃ分からないかもね
Maybe someone as entirely mediocre as you wouldn't understand.
嗚呼よく似合う そのかもなく不可もないメロディ
Ah, it suits you so well, a melody that's neither good nor bad.
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ 頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
Shut up, shut up, shut up, our brains work differently, so there's no problem.
It feels like you were in a massage!
マッサージされてる！ I feel so good! Yeah!
I'm getting a massage! I feel so good! Yeah!
All righty then, the scores in again. Let's see what you got!
応援します、じゃじゃん！
We're rooting for you, ta-da!
She got 77.994! That's literally 78.
She got 77.994! That's practically 78!
That's so good!
Alright, well, who's left? We only have one person left!
I'm the kid!
いきなさい！早く！Watashi mou ii sing?
Go! Hurry! Am I going to sing?
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko because the world is just that cruel. 世界は残酷です。
I am going to be singing "Akuma no Ko" because the world is just that cruel. The world is cruel.
先生、もう本当にもう一回やってください。
Sensei, please do your absolute best once more.
はい。
Yes.
優しくしてください。強くて...強くて。
Please be gentle with me. Strong... strong...
All right, you ready?
I'm scared.
Yosh! Jaan! Music start!
Yosh! Ta-da! Music start!
鉄の弾が正義の証明 貫けば英雄に近づいた
An iron bullet is proof of justice; if pierced through, I grew closer to a hero.
その目を閉じて触れてみれば 同じ形同じ体温の悪魔
If you close your eyes and touch it, an evil with the same shape and body temperature.
僕はダメで あいつはいいの？ そこに壁があっただけなのに
Why is it bad for me, but okay for them? When all there was was a wall in the way.
生まれてしまった運命嘆くな 僕らはみんな自由なんだから
Don't lament the fate we were born with, because we are all free.
鳥のように羽があれば どこへだって行けるけど 帰る場所がなければ
If we had wings like birds, we could go anywhere, but if there's no place to return to,
きっとどこへも行けない ただただ生きるのは嫌だ
we surely can't go anywhere. I hate just simply living.
世界は残酷だ それでも君を愛よ
The world is cruel, but I still love you.
なにを犠牲にしても それでも君を守るよ 間違いだとしても疑ったりしない
Even if I sacrifice anything, I will still protect you. Even if it's a mistake, I won't doubt it.
正しさとは自分のこと 強く信じることだ
Righteousness is believing strongly in one's own self.
Daro? How do you feel? How is it refreshing?
Right? How do you feel? Isn't it refreshing?
Refreshing, right?
It was great. 素晴らしい体験をさせていただきました。
It was great. I was allowed to experience something wonderful.
All right, I feel like the scores are in. Shall we see? Jaan-jaan!
All right, I feel like the scores are in. Shall we see? Ta-da!
She did so good! 77.716 pts!
My big toe still hurts so bad. I know.
泣いたがってます。滝田さん、ありがとうございました。
She's crying for more. Tachita-san, thank you very much.
ありがとうございました。いた気持ちよかったです。バイバイ。
Thank you very much. It felt pleasantly painful. Bye-bye!
Okay then! I present to you the final scores.
Ta-da! Ta-da!
The one and only first place with 151,858 points is...
Ouro Kronii!
Oh, I wish I got a massage for my left side, too,
that would have been so nice. But, you know, I'm so happy that we got to suffer together.
Yeah, let's get back to the lore!
Not yet.
Not yet. Not yet.
Wait, actually, yeah, let's get back to the lore!
Yeah, we should get back to the lore.
Yeah, I think it's time, yeah?
It's time for the punishment game!
Stepsun, please prepare. Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, so this today was like a super sour drink. Yeah. I heard it's a sour drink.
It's... It smells... It smells healthy.
Wait, it smells good, though.
It smells ass.
It's like... like ume? Maybe? Is it ume? It smells ume.
Yeah.
Kusuguttakunai, chotto.
It tickles a bit.
Da fukenkou no futari de...
As the two unhealthy ones...
Sabato-suta! Kanpaii!
Sabato-suta! Cheers!
That sounds wonderful.
Umeh!
That's actually really good.
Really? Wow.
It tastes better after I've been more...
It tastes better after I've been more time.
My face is turning into that lemon meme, you know? Like the lemon face just immerses in. Yeah, futari mo sah.
My face is turning into that lemon meme, you know? Like the lemon face just immerses in. Yeah, both of you sah.
I feel so... probably healthy.
Very healthy and guys!
Okay, so we're going to return to the live performance, and the second half includes new songs, so let's keep it going, guys! Woohoo!
Hey, you guys are fine. Okay, let's get a move on.
Just... just get a move on.
You still... you really... I'm fine now. Dabu- dabu yokunatta yo.
You still... you really... I'm fine now. I'm getting much better.
全然もっと背中押しても血が出るくらいに
Even if you push my back until it bleeds—
嘘だいわ、何にすがってあつらえて
what a lie! What did I cling to and customize,
期待した、確かばっかだった
hoping for? It was all just certainty.
ねぇ、不甲斐ないアップビートに
Hey, to a spineless upbeat,
不来印なアンチナイショギに
to an unbranded anti-secret show,
最小限過して、毎秒綺麗にに
keeping it to a minimum, every second neatly
詰まる特等人生ずっと地味
packed into a front-row life, forever plain.
美し痛い大し、無死できないのだ
Beautiful, painful, big-deal, impossible to ignore—
いっそ腹立たしい腹立たしいそろそろ
it's so infuriating, so infuriating, soon
悪足がざまに
struggling in vain,
ライトの反対側不審に
on the opposite side of the light, suspiciously,
霊合起こるじゃっく足
an exceptional Jack-step—
切り離せない関係飛ばしてしまいたいわ
I want to blow past this inseparable relationship!
これわいはゆるデート、スピードと
This is a so-called date, with speed and
スイッチひとつ明日の生命よ
a single switch, tomorrow's life,
生命に乗せてんだ
loaded onto life itself.
何にもないダイライツ、気がついた
Nothing at all, die-lights, noticing
ミニゲームアクシデントに
mini-game accidents,
ずっと旬々です
always in season.
ダイダイあなたのことを私ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Dai-dai-dai-dai-dai-kirai of you! I hate you so, so, so, so much!
お世辞願わんさいけないもうバイバイバイバイバイしちゃ
Don't you dare ask for flattery, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye—
だめない？
shouldn't I?
予定通りの暗がりのことをあなた
Scheduled darkness, you—
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
dai-dai-dai-dai-dai-kirai!
見つかった愛で深まって
Found love deepening,
一リナシなシングモシモ
one-man-show, if it's true,
知ら立たされれば並べでも
if you made it known, even side-by-side,
ニコチンパシー
nicotine-pathy,
愛して違づいて結末は
loving, approaching, the conclusion is
ボミストにサンキューハメキシオーシン
to the vomist, thank you, Hame-kyoushin,
あと味消えてくれないわ
aftertaste won't fade away!
よしがしい、これが不気味巻きちら
Goodness gracious, scattering this eerie
ばるばるいいごね
whining all over—
だけどだけどその本性は
but, but, its true nature has
善悪の区別もつかないの
no concept of good and evil!
原点の日奇跡通りのステップように
Stepping as miraculous as the origin,
巻かれて
wrapped up,
障害ダイダイダイダイ
obstacle dai-dai-dai-dai!
クソだな、どうせどん底に
What crap, anyway, in the depths of despair,
叩き落とされちゃった
knocked right down.
人は鏡なんです、心の
People are mirrors, the heart's
器依ぞんは両縁で
vessel's reliance is on both rims,
シャットダウンしても隙間とう
even if you shut down, the gaps
俺の要素が深いない
don't reach my depth!
問題はいつのことを切り離した方が楽なのにね
The problem is, it would be easier if I could just cut off the past...
大体 あなたのこと 大嫌い
Basically, I really hate you.
お前が情けない もはやバイバイバイバイバイ
You're pathetic, it's already bye-bye-bye-bye-bye.
シャッフルナイト もうよそう 昨日の夜にバイバイバイバイバイ
Shuffle night, enough of last night, bye-bye-bye-bye-bye.
出逢いが違って行けば 末路はゴミクズ
If our paths had crossed differently, our end would be trash.
天気は盲目 あと味一緒喰いたくないわ
The weather is blind, and the aftertaste is the same, I don't want to taste it.
あと味一緒喰いたくないわ
I don't want to taste it.
簡単な英語しかわかんない
I only know simple English,
踊りの大好き 健康第一
I love to dance, health comes first.
H A L F
H-A-L-F
憧れとコンプレックス 大渋滞
Admiration and complexes, a huge traffic jam.
カーステでノリノリ
Car stereo lifts my spirits,
カースートは飽き飽き
already sick of this routine.
試されてる いつもいつでも 恵まれているかどうかを
I'm being tested, anytime, always, whether I'm blessed or not.
楽しくしていたい 泣きたくないから 問い正す 神様がいなくても
I just want to have fun, I don't want to cry, I ask, even if there's no god.
もうカッコつけてくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to act cool.
そのまま そのまま 降り注ぐひかり
Just as it is, this light pouring down,
ねえ 半分なんて思ったことないぜ
hey, I never thought I was half.
そのまま そのまま 突き進むひかり
Just as this is, that light piercing forward,
いじわるなんかじゃ止まらない
I won't stop just because of petty things.
笑わせたいのに 上手にできない
I want to make you laugh, but I can't do it well.
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame anyone.
生まれてみたいから 生まれてきただけ
I just wanted to be born, so I was born.
新しい普通と幸せ そんなに遠くはないでしょ
A new normal and happiness shouldn't be that far away.
それでもいまも誰かが 打ち放す悲しみと怒りの H A L F
Even so, still now, someone is firing off sadness and anger, H-A-L-F.
損をしたり ちょっとつらい そんな日もあるけど
Taking losses and feeling a bit painful, there are days like that too.
いばらの道で花が咲くなら 絶対見逃さない
If flowers bloom on a thorny road, I definitely can't miss it.
もうカッコつけてくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to act cool.
そのまま そのまま 降り注ぐひかり
Just as it is, this light pouring down,
ねえ 半分なんて思ったことないぜ
hey, I never thought I was half.
そのまま そのまま 突き進むひかり
Just as this is, that light piercing forward.
損をしたり ちょっとつらい そんな日もあるけど いばらの道で花が咲くなら 絶対見逃さない
Taking losses, feeling a bit painful, if flowers bloom on a thorny road, I'll never miss it.
H A L F
H-A-L-F
損をしたり 衝突らい
Taking losses and clashes,
そんな日もあるけど いばらの道で花が咲くなら
there are days like that too, if flowers bloom on a thorny road.
絶対見逃さない
I definitely can't miss it.
もうカッコつけてくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to act cool.
そのまま そのまま 降り注ぐひかり
Just as it is, this light pouring down,
ねえ 半分なんて思ったことないぜ
hey, I never thought I was half.
そのまま そのまま 突き進むひかり
Just as this is, that light piercing forward.
H A L F
H-A-L-F
I don't want nobody to get killed,
I'll come and get you,
I am always ready to fight.
So don't take all of the blame,
we were all swept away.
Don't take all of the weight you always do.
There will always be something you cannot control.
We will overcome, your salvation has begun.
No signs, no lights,
such a mess all over.
Don't kill your hopes, you make me realize who I need.
I'll be there, hold on.
They'll change you somehow.
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn.
Before you can be turned, illusions are torn.
The fallen angels you run with don't know,
it is our pain that makes us all human after all.
Warm old sepia photographs show
our fragile precious world.
Must protect it, respond to the call.
Are they really deep inside your head?
Do they control you like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead, come in with me.
Let me free the wings of your soul, can make it fly.
We've been waiting here just to make you whole again.
No more hating, see I have always been your friend.
No signs, no lights,
such a mess all over.
Don't kill your hopes, you make me realize who I need.
I'll be there, hold on.
They'll change you somehow.
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn.
The shadows appear, illusions are born.
The fallen angels you run with don't know,
it is our pain that makes us all human after all.
Torn old sepia photographs show
our fragile precious world.
Must discard it, respond to the call.
If you wanna fight with me, then go ahead fight with me.
'Cos all I wanna do is help you man.
You will be the death of me.
The power of our army has been cut with a scythe,
and if we lose you to them we may never survive.
You can leave, but you must first believe.
Just one step at a time and keep your head up boy
and you'll be free.
How was that so far?
That was good.
How did- how did you feel?
That was good. How do you feel?
You guys like how it's been going so far on the songs?
We just had all of our duo songs!
And we also went through a variety part and...
And everything else.
How are you guys doing? Does it still hurt?
I don't know how I- I don't know how I danced with this foot.
Ah, how are you guys? You're probably fine.
You're not worried about you at all. How about you?
My foot still hurts, but it's okay.
Yay!
There is a surprise at the end.
But before that, we have an announcement about merchandise!
Check this out!
Look at the key visual!
It's the hololive English Promise 2nd Anniversary Celebration Merch! We're releasing merchandise to commemorate our second anniversary!
Let's take turns introducing the merch, shall we?
So first up is...
a frame art board of our wonderful key visual for the Promise 2nd Anniversary!
The frame part uses luxurious, sparkling paper,
and the printed illustration turns this into a high-quality piece of art. Oh my! You definitely don't want to miss the chance to add it to your collection or room!
And guess what? You can even hang it on the wall!
On the wall! On the wall!
Next up are the collection cards for each of Promise!
These cards feature an attractive design that are foil-stamped on the front, and you can treat each card individually, so be sure to collect all of them!
Next, we also have ring necklaces!
This design includes key references and motifs for each of us.
You can use it as either a ring or a necklace, so feel free to change it up depending on the occasion!
And next, we have special porcelain tumblers with our designs on them!
It features our talent colors on top of a black base.
They're designed to have a unified look, and I bet it'll look so cool if you use several of these tumblers together in like a drinking party or something!
Okay, last one!
And lastly, we have a 2-way tote bag!
It's a 2-way design that can be used as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag. Ooh, that's actually really cool!
It's even designed to be used as a carry-on bag too, perfect for traveling and convenience!
And to top it off, it has many pockets that will definitely be useful for storing small items like us! Oh my god! Yes!
And that concludes the Promise 2nd Anniversary merch introduction!
Yay! Introduction!
And with that, we're finally at the very last part. Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there would be a special, you know, surprise or announcement earlier. Would you like to hear what it is? Yes!
Oh, but, but before that-
But before we announce it, it's time for a stage change!
Stage change!
Ah, wait! Don't, don't, don't, don't touch it!
Everything's changing!
No, IRyS, that's mine! Don't push!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, we got it, we got it. Okay.
Oh, I'm getting... I'm getting claustrophobic.
Oh, I'm gonna be sick!
Okay, it's open! Oh, see the light! Oh...
Oh, my goodness!
Okay. Ah... Nice. Ah, that's nice.
I feel fresh air. Okay.
All righty. Well, ladies, it is time for our final announcement.
Final announcement?!
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Finally releasing! It's called "Run Back 'Round".
Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song, and it's really cool, really catchy. It's quite different to, you know, a lot of the original songs that we as Promise have put out before. So, different genre.
Yeah! We hope that you guys will listen to it lots. The chorus part is quite hype and honestly quite easy to remember,
so I feel like, you know, hopefully it becomes an earworm and you can put it on loop over and over and over again.
That's our big new reveal!
Are you excited? IRyS is excited! IRyS is so excited!
Well, I think, I think all that's left is for us to perform our new song.
What? We're going to perform it here? Oh, here! Floating, floating here in the city!
But before we go, do you have any final thoughts about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this, this Promise.
And you know, it was a lot of fun singing all those songs with you guys, you know, different duets. And the... I just really like the fact that we have a hideout now!
We do! We finally have our hideout now! We have our tour too!
We have our celebration! Catch you at the bug!
Yeah. I guess it's in a fabulous location. Imagine how expensive the rent is!
Yeah, we need to pay for it. Well, IRyS pays for it. All good!
So, yeah, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
Yeah, I'm just really thankful that, you know, we're still here after two years, and you know, I hope everyone continues to support Promise. Thank you guys!
And here's to many, many more! Yay!
I could say the same thing. I'm just going to steal everyone and say that it's been great being with all of you for two years.
And, you know, now we get to have this cool hideout and this awesome song that we get to show everyone! So, yay!
Are we ready? Yes, I'm ready. Let's go!
Ready? Set, not! Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round,
don't stop now.
Up with the moonlight,
down in the streetlights.
Looking for a spotlight,
making my move.
(Woah) I'm running,
(Woah) 行こう！
(Woah) Ikou!
Days like a whirlwind,
don't stop coming.
Got me in a tailspin,
what can I do?
(Woah) Keep running,
(Woah) 行こう！
(Woah) Ikou!
Lost and found, back to where I started,
I won't stay down, trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud, take it to the limit,
so stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round, got to keep believing,
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah-woah, oh,
woah-woah, oh,
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah-woah, oh,
Sparks on the pavement,
dreams in the distance.
Gotta be relentless,
faster than sound!
(Woah) Keep running,
(Woah) 行こう！
(Woah) Ikou!
Oh yeah...
Lock it and load it,
僕らは explosive
we're explosive!
Swifter and lighter,
明日もきっと brighter
tomorrow's gonna be brighter!
Oh yeah...
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round
it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round,
got to keep believing,
Right back 'round!
I run back 'round,
I know where I'm going,
Day and night I'm running
Nothing's gonna stop me now!
Hoo...
Woah, oh, oh!
止まらないよ!
Won't stop now!
Woah, oh, oh!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
走って、走って、走って
Running, running, running,
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!
始まるよ, I'm coming around, I've got a dream just waiting, now
It's starting, I'm coming around, I've got a dream just waiting, now
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Everybody
Woah, oh, oh!
Yeah, everybody
Yeah, everybody, come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Woah, oh, oh!